几点了
What time is it?
刚过五点半
Just past 5:30.
走吧
Let's go.
昨晚没看见那个
Didn't see that last night.
没看见什么
Didn't see what?
还在走
Still going.
但看起来像是队尾了
Looks like the end of them, though.
走了一夜啊
All damn night.
至少尼根够聪明
At least Negan's smart enough
没让那些东西接近我们
not to let that mess anywhere near us.
肥乔至少还是有点用处的
Fat Joey's good for something, at least.
是说他很能吃蛋糕吗
What, eating cake?
他负责给尸群改道
He rigged the herdway.
只是转转
Just trips.
没什么大不了的
Nothing fancy.
就像游击队
Guerilla kind of stuff.
像什么
What kind of stuff?
战争中的游击队  白痴
As in warfare, idiot.
上个月搜刮拿到的枪
Those demo sticks from that run last month,
新人那里拿到的火箭筒
the RPGs from the new guys.
也许能削减数量
Maybe it takes it down.
除掉它们
Takes them out.
好  很少了
All right, it's a trickle.
-我们走  -终于
- Let's go. - Finally.
谢天谢地
Thank Christ.
做记号
Making a trail.
我觉得我们接近了
I think we're close.
我们该下车了  剩下的路跟着走
We should bail out, follow the rest of the way,
看看能看见什么
see what we can see.
我
I, uh...
怎么做
How?
一般摔不会受伤
It isn't usually the fall that gets us.
抵抗才会受伤  顺势滚滚就好
It's trying to fight it. Run with it or roll with it.
卡车速度够慢了
The truck's going slow enough.
我们会在盲区
We'll be in the blind spot.
我们可以跟着别的车过去
We can race behind one of the other cars.
如果我搞砸了  我们被抓了
I-I-If -- If I screw up and we get caught --
会没事的  我们现在得下车了
It'll be fine. We just got to go now.
好吧  先给我演示一下
Okay. Show me first.
"先给我演示一下"
"Show me first"...
好吧  小伙子们  卸货  搬进去
Okay, boys, let's get this haul unloaded and inside.
我要回去了  自己泻点火
I want to get back in there and unload a little myself.
尼根  得跟你谈谈改道的事
Negan, need to talk to you about redirect.
改道怎么了
What about the redirect?
搞砸了
It got screwed up.
我们现在在处理  但外面一团糟
We're on it now, but it's a mess out there.
那是谁的工作
And whose job was that?
一个背包和一个帐篷
...A pack and a tent...
该死
Aw, damn.
我还以为他们装得满满的
I thought they packed this up tight.
别担心
Ah, no worries.
他们还会送更多来的
Plenty more where this came from.
对吧
Right?
该死
Son of a bitch!
怎么回事
What the hell?
后退  放下武器
Stay back! Drop your weapons.
我只想要尼根
I only want Negan.
他杀了我的朋友们
He killed my friends.
别人没必要死
No one else needs to die.
靠
Damn.
你真可爱
You are adorable.
你选了这把枪是因为它看起来很酷吗
Did you pick that gun 'cause it looks cool?
绝对是  对吧
You totally did, right?
孩子  我不会撒谎
Kid, I ain't gonna lie --
你吓死老子了
you scare the shit outta me.
小子
Kid!
德怀特
Dwight.
后退
Back off.
那是对待新客人的方式吗
Is that any way to treat our new guest?
来吧  孩子
Come on, kid.
我带你四处转转
I will show you around.
《行尸走肉》
来吧  孩子
Come on, kid.
我带你四处转转
I'll show you around.
你跟你爸爸一样  都有令人讨厌的眼神
You know, you do the same damn stink-eye as your dad,
不过只有一半讨厌  因为
except it's only half as good 'cause...
你知道的  你
well, you know, you're...
少了只眼睛
missing an eye.
真的吗
Really?
你真的不拉我的手吗
You're really not gonna take my hand?
因为你还有手是你走运
'Cause you're lucky you even still have a hand.
你的伙伴达里尔也是
Same as your boy Daryl over here,
现在我想起来了
now that I think about it.
工作怎么样  达里尔
How's the job going, Daryl?
对你来说够劲吗
Hot enough for you?
是啊  一只手会很难工作
Yeah, it'd be tough with one arm.
聪明的孩子
Ah, smart kid.
现在跟我来
Now come with me.
德怀特  你带上达里尔
Dwighty-boy, why don't you grab Daryl,
去厨房  准备点吃的
take him to the kitchen, do a little grub prep.
新计划  伙计们
New plan, boys.
死人烧了  晚点再卸货
Let's burn the dead, unload the truck later.
天啊  我今天都没时间
Damn, I am not gonna have time
干我的老婆们了
to screw any of my wives today.
也许有时间干一个吧
I mean, maybe one.
来吧
Come on.
你要对我做什么
What are you gonna do to me?
第一
Number one,
别打破我对你的印象
do not shatter my image of you.
你是个硬汉
You're a badass.
天不怕地不怕
You're not scared of shit.
别怕我
Don't be scared of me.
这令人失望
It's a disappointment.
第二
Number two...
你真想让我毁掉惊喜吗
you really want me to ruin the surprise?
去你的  孩子
Screw you, kid.
说真的
Seriously.
去你的
Screw you.
(关门前一定要进行夜间检查)
来看看
Check this out.
救世军去外面
The Saviors have gone out into the world
与行尸斗争
and fought the dead
带回来了一些很好的东西
and come back with some really good stuff.
如果你们努力工作  遵守规定
Some of that stuff can be yours
有些东西可以归你们
if you work hard and play by the rules.
今天  每个人晚餐都能吃到新鲜蔬菜
Today, everybody gets fresh vegetables at dinner.
不需要工分
No points needed.
看见了吗
You see that?
尊重
Respect.
很酷吧
Cool, huh?
他们还跪着吗
They still on their knees?
还原
As you were!
我想给你看一些我打了B+
Hey, I wanted to show you a few potentials
或是更高分数的潜力地点
I've rated B-plus or higher.
我知道我们要去哪里
I know where we're going.
虽然我感到你十分确定
While I'm picking up a high level of certainty,
但为了不疏忽  我还是要提到
I'd be remiss if I didn't mention
在对周边区域的深入分析后
that after a thorough analysis of the grid,
打叉了所有我们搜寻过的地点
X'ing out any places we've already combed,
我相信我准确定位了
I do believe I've bull's-eye'd
一些值得考虑的地点  来进行手头的特定任务
some worth considering for the specific task at hand.
什么
What?
为尼根找东西
Finding goods for Negan.
不  我们才不为那混蛋做事
No, we're not doing shit for that cabron.
你不要出去为救世军找东西吗
You're not going out to find stuff for the Saviors?
为什么
Why not?
没什么好抵抗的  罗西塔
There's no fighting it, Rosita.
也许我们该一起去
Perhaps we should all travel together.
我愿意
I'm down.
四个人在大海里更容易捞针
We come across a haystack, four POVs could draw out whatever we're looking for.
我们自己可以的
We're fine on our own.
我知道你不喜欢
I know you don't like it
你不想听我说
and you don't want to hear it from me,
但我们得为他们找东西
but we got to produce for them.
这就像是交税
This is like taxes.
-喂  -过来
- Hey. - Come here.
喂
Hey.
你可以一直对我生气
You can keep acting pissed at me,
但这不是我做的
but I didn't do this.
而是瑞克
Rick did.
你觉得你可以做得更好
You think you can do better.
是的
Yes.
当然啦
Sure.
你肯定给自己藏了
No, I bet you already have a whole truck-load full of stuff
一卡车东西  是吧
hidden out there for yourself, huh?
去拿吧
Go get it.
去交税  别他妈来烦我
Pay your taxes, and leave me the hell alone.
走吧
Let's go.
女士们
Ladies.
别管这孩子
Don't mind the kid.
我知道
I know.
在你来的地方  每个女人
Every woman where you're from
穿得都像是汽修店里的会计
dresses like they do the books at an auto shop.
你会想看看她们的乳头的
You're gonna want to look at their titties.
没事  我不介意
It's cool. I won't mind.
她们不介意  你自便
They won't mind. Knock yourself out.
我能和你谈谈吗  爱妻
Can I talk to you for a minute, dear wife?
不用拘束  小子
Make yourself comfortable, kid.
安珀和马克怎么了
What happened with Amber and Mark?
你不在这里时我们所谈论的事
What we talk about when you're not here
与你无关
is none of your business.
好吧
Fair play.
你知道我听说了什么吗
You want to know what I heard?
我听说马克翘掉了改道的班
I heard that Mark skipped out on redirect duty
就为了和安珀幽会
to be with Amber.
我得知道这是不是真的
I need to know if it's true.
我立规矩是有原因的
There are rules for a reason.
人要是死了什么都是一场空
Nothing matters if you're dead.
亲爱的  你在这里是因为你懂这点
You, my dear, are here because you get that.
她只是犯了个错误
She made a mistake.
别难为她
Go easy on her.
冷静点
Calm the hell down.
我打过你们中的任何一个吗
I ever hit one of you?
没有
No.
但我了解你
But I know you.
你有更可怕的手段
There's worse.
瞧瞧你啊
Well, look at you!
下次继续
To be continued.
安珀  宝贝
Amber, baby.
你知道我不希望这里有人是
You know I don't want anyone here
不情不愿地留下的  对吗
that doesn't want to be here, right?
假如你想离开我
So if you want to leave
回到马克身边...
and go back to Mark...
你可以
you can.
但你知道什么事是不可以做的吗
But what can't you do?
背着你乱搞
Cheat on you.
完全正确
That is exactly right.
你不能
You can't...
背着我乱搞
cheat on me.
有大把妞儿想取代你的位置
There's plenty of other gals who would love to take your place,
我也能想到几个适合你做的工作
and there's a few job openings that I can think of.
你想回到马克和你妈妈身边吗
You want to go back to Mark and your mom?
我可以安排你们三个做同一个工作
Hell, I'll put you all on the same job.
不
No.
我...
I --
我会留下来的
I'll stay.
我...我很抱歉
I'm...I'm sorry.
你知道那意味着什么吧
You know what that means, right?
知...道
Ye-- Yes.
我爱你  尼根
I love you, Negan.
你当然爱我了  亲爱的
Oh, of course you do, darlin'.
我不知道你在哭什么
I don't know why you're crying.
你会过得舒舒服服的
It's all gonna work out aces for you.
你能去帮我把卡森喊来吗
Will you get Carson for me?
-好的  -你刚刚看见了吗
- Yeah. - Did you see that?
我没为难她
Wasn't hard on her,
即便我...总体来说不是个好说话的人
even though I am... very hard in general.
你就是个混蛋
You're an asshole.
我知道
I know.
但诡异的是  你依然喜欢我
But the messed-up thing is, you like me anyway.
你知道真相的  和我一样
You know the truth, just like me.
卡尔  你能帮我端着这个盘子吗
Carl, will you grab this tray for me?
你为什么把他带来这里
Why do you got him here?
你不在这里时我们所谈论的事
What we talk about when you're not here...
与你无关
is none of your business.
别逼我把这根牙签
Do not make me put this toothpick
插进他仅剩的那只眼睛里
through the only eye he has.
你跟德怀特走
You go with Dwight.
他会给你找个拖把
He'll get you a mop.
小德怀特...
Dwighty boy...
把炉子生起来
fire up that furnace.
我一会儿就下去
I'll be down in a few.
是时候往日重现了
Time for a little deja vu.
来吧  孩子
Come on, kid.
我们只有今天一天的时间搜寻物资了
We have today and only today to find somethin'.
他们可能明天就回来了
They could be back by tomorrow.
也可能现在就回来了
Could be back now.
(继续向前走  等着你的只有麻烦)
恨某个人...这算是罪吗
Hating somebody -- is that a sin?
不算
No.
不一定算
Well, not necessarily.
想法只是想法而已
Thoughts are just thoughts.
重要的是我们的行为
It's our actions that matter in the end.
我恨瑞克
I hate Rick.
他曾经是个警察  那又怎样
He was a cop. Fine.
不该他管事的
He shouldn't be in charge.
我母亲  她...是国会的
My mother, she -- she served in Congress.
她领导人们
She led people.
她能发掘人们的闪光点
She brought out the good in people.
瑞克发掘了我的闪光点
Rick brought out the good in me.
怎么发掘的  靠欺负你吗
How? By bullying you?
是有点
A little.
但主要还是靠启发我
But mostly by inspiring me.
他不仅仅是保住了大家的命
He didn't just keep people alive.
他还让我们团结在了一起
He brought us all together.
他不完美  但他是个有主见的人
He's not perfect, but he's a man who finds his way.
他可没有保住所有人的命  加百利
He didn't keep everybody alive, Gabriel.
我母亲  我父亲  我兄弟...
My mother, my father, my brother...
那不是他的错
It wasn't his fault.
他到了这里  他们就死了
He got here, they died.
也许别人还活着是因为他到了这里
Or maybe other people didn't die because he got here.
也许我们不该袭击那个哨站
Or maybe we shouldn't have attacked that outpost
-那样格伦...  -我们事先不知情
- and then Glenn... - We don't know!
不可能知道
We can't.
没机会知道
We don't get to.
事已至此...
We're here now...
我们可以着眼于未来
and we can look to the future.
什么未来
What future?
他管事的话我们没有未来
There's no future with him in charge.
我现在禁不住想...
The thing I can't stop thinking is that...
也许目前能发生在我们身上的最好的事...
maybe the only good thing that could happen for us now...
就是他回不来了
is he never makes it back.
停车
Stop the car.
你所说的话...
What you're saying --
不会让你成为罪人
it doesn't make you a sinner.
但的确让你成为了一个彻头彻尾的混蛋
But it does make you a tremendous shit.
但这只是一时
Just for now.
人是可以改变的
It doesn't have to be terminal.
我要回去了
I'm gonna go back.
所有那些女人  真的都是你的...
Are all of those women actually your --
妻子  是的
Wives? Yeah.
我一直梦想着能睡一大群不同的女人
Always wanted to screw a whole bunch of different women.
为什么吊死在一棵树上呢
I mean, why settle for just one?
为什么要遵守老规矩呢
Why follow the same old rules?
何不让生活变得更美好些
Why not make life better?
说到这个...
Speaking of...
坐吧
sit.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
开始干什么
Started on what?
我想加深一下对你的了解  卡尔
I want to get to know you a little better, Carl.
为什么
Why?
自己想想
Work it out.
你很聪明
You're smart.
实际上  我要告诉你你有多聪明
In fact, I'm gonna tell you just how smart you are,
以免你自己还没意识到
in case you don't already know.
我以为你这年龄的孩子只会闷闷不乐
See, I'd expect a kid your age to be moping around,
无所事事
not doing a damn thing,
就知道为错过舞会而哭哭啼啼
except crying about missing the prom.
但你  你却肩负起重任
But you -- you go on a mission.
你找到了我  杀了我两个手下
You find me, you kill two of my men,
而且你足够聪明  知道我不会放过你
and you're smart enough to know that I'm not gonna let this slide.
我...我说不下去了
I can't -- I can't do it.
感觉像是对着生日礼物说话似的
It's like talking to a birthday present.
你得把你脸上那个鬼玩意取下来
You got to take that crap off your face.
我想看看礼物里包着的是什么
I want to see what Grandma got me.
-不  -两个手下
- No. - Two men!
两个...手下
Two...men.
惩罚
Punishment.
你真的想激怒我吗
Do you really want to piss me off?
快了
Almost there.
把头发从脸上撩开
Get that hair out of your face.
让我看看
Let me see.
老天爷
Christ!
真恶心
That is disgusting.
怪不得你要遮起来了
No wonder you cover that up.
你自己看过吗
Have you seen it?
你照过镜子吗
I mean, have you looked in the mirror?
真是太他妈恶心了
That is gross as hell.
我都能看到你的眼窝了
I can see your socket.
我想摸摸
I want to touch it.
来嘛  能给我摸摸吗
Oh, come on. Can I touch it?
靠
Damn.
老天啊  孩子
Holy hell, kid.
听着...
Look...
我只是...
I just --
你很容易让人忘了...
It's easy to forget that you're...
你只是个孩子
just a kid.
我不是故意要伤你心的  我...
And I didn't mean to hurt your feelings or anything. I --
-我只是在开玩笑  -算了
- I was just screwing around. - Just forget it.
进
Come in.
抱歉打搅  先生  但是
I'm sorry to interrupt, sir, but, uh...
您把露西尔落在货车那边了
you left Lucille out by the truck.
真的吗
Seriously?
我从没那样做过
I never do that.
我猜是小朋友开冲锋枪
I guess a kid firing a machine gun
分散了我的注意力
is a little bit of a distraction.
不开玩笑  你看起来酷毙了
All jokes aside, you look rad as hell.
换做是我  就不会遮住
I wouldn't cover that shit up.
女孩子可能不感冒
It may not be a hit with the ladies,
但我向你保证
but I swear to you,
长成这样  没人敢惹你
no one is gonna screw with you looking like that.
没人敢  先生
No, sir.
肥乔  是你帮我把她一路拿过来的吗
Fat Joseph, did you carry her all the way up here for me?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
拿的时候温柔吗
Were you gentle?
体贴吗
Were you kind?
像对待女士一样对她吗
Did you treat her like a lady?
是的  先生
Mm, yes. Yes, sir.
你像对待女士一样爱抚她的私处吗
Did you pet her little pussy like a lady?
我开玩笑的  伙计
I'm just screwing around, man.
球棍哪有什么私处
A baseball bat doesn't have a pussy.
滚出去
Get the hell out.
看到了吧
Now, you see?
我说的就是这个
That's what I'm talking about.
男人都互相打趣
Men breaking each other's balls.
这种事该是你爸教你的
This is the shit your dad's supposed to be teaching you.
你平时有什么娱乐
What do you like to do for fun?
喜欢音乐吗
You like music?
我要你给我唱首歌
I want you to sing me a song.
什么
What?
是的
Yeah.
你用冲锋枪打死我两个手下
You mowed down two of my men with a machine gun.
我想要点交换
I want something in return for that.
-给我唱首歌  -我...
- Sing me a song. - I...
-我想不起来  -放屁
- I -- I can't think of any. - Bullshit!
你妈妈给你唱过什么歌
What'd your mom used to sing you?
你爸开车时听什么歌
What'd your dad play in the car?
-开始唱  -好  好
- Start singing. - Okay, okay.
好
Okay.
*你是我的阳光*
*You are my sunshine*
继续
Go on.
*我唯一的阳光*
*My only sunshine*
*你使我快乐*
*You make me happy*
*即使天空阴霾*
*When skies are gray*
不要被我打搅了  年轻人
Do not let me distract you, young man.
*你不知道*
*You'll...Never know...*
*亲爱的  我有多爱你*
*Dear, how much I love you*
*所以请不要带走我的阳光*
*So...please don't take my...sunshine away*
唱得不错
That's pretty good.
露西尔也喜欢听歌
Lucille loves being sung to.
这可能是唯一一件  比砸碎脑壳
It's about the only thing she loves more
更让她喜欢的事了
than bashing in brains.
奇怪吧
Weird, huh?
这首歌是你妈妈唱给你的吧
Did your mother sing that to you?
她现在在哪
Where is she now?
靠
Damn.
死了  是吧
Dead, huh?
你亲眼目睹了吗
You see it happen?
我开枪打死了她
I shot her...
在转化之前...
before it could...
靠  难怪你是个成长中的小连环杀手
Damn, no wonder you're a little serial killer in the making.
顺便说  那也是互相打趣的一个好例子
That was an example of breaking balls, by the way.
来吧孩子  起来
Come on, kid. Get up.
应该准备好了
It should be ready.
什么准备好了
What should be ready?
烙铁
The iron.
帮我拿着
Hold that for me.
你们知道规矩
You know the deal.
接下来你们要看到的一幕比较难接受
What's about to happen is gonna be hard to watch.
我也不想这么做
I don't want to do it.
我希望能无视规矩  让这事过去算了
I wish I could just ignore the rules and let it slide,
可是不行
but I can't.
为什么
Why?
有规矩才能活命
The rules keep us alive.
说  得  对
That...is...right.
我们活了下来
We survive.
我们保护他人
We provide security to others.
我们让世界重回文明
We bring civilization back to this world.
我们是救世军
We are the Saviors.
但没有规矩  我们就做不到
But we can't do that without rules.
规矩是一切运转的前提
Rules are what make it all work.
我知道这很难
I know it's not easy.
但总是有工作要做
But there's always work.
一切都是有代价的
There is always a cost.
在这里  如果你想逃避责任
Here, if you try to skirt it,
想着偷工减料
if you try to cut that corner...
那你就要受烙铁之刑
...then it is the iron for you.
起立
On your feet.
小德
D...
马克  抱歉了
Mark...I'm sorry.
但规矩就是规矩
But it is what it is.
也不是太糟糕  对吧
Ah, that wasn't so bad, now, was it?
天啊  他尿裤了
Jesus. He pissed himself.
打扫干净
Clean that up.
医生  我完事了  你来吧
Doc, I'm all done. Do your thing.
这个孬种晕过去了
Well, the pussy passed out.
但事情解决了  我们两清了
But it's settled -- we're square.
没事了
Everything is cool.
就让马克的脸每天提醒他
Let Mark's face be a daily reminder to him
提醒所有人  规矩很重要
and to everyone else that the rules matter.
希望大家今天都学到了东西
I hope that we all learned something today,
因为我再也不想
because I don't ever...
做这种事了
want to have to do that again.
很疯狂是吧
Some crazy shit, huh?
你可能会觉得我是个疯子
You probably think I'm a lunatic.
走吧
Come on.
让我们想想怎么处理你
Let's go figure out what to do with you.
[拉丁语]
我不想回到这
I didn't want to come back here.
我不...
I don't...
不行
No.
我请你帮我做一颗子弹
I asked you to make me a bullet.
你答应了我
You said yes.
那就给我做一颗子弹
So make me a bullet.
没错  我当时是答应了你
You're right. I said yes.
但那只是
But that...
一时激动
was peak heat of the moment.
在中间时刻  我深入思考了
Uh, in the intervening hours, I've been taking a deep dive
其他选择和意外情况
into other options and contingencies,
想要复盘找出
trying to game out any iteration
任何开始这项行动的理由
in which charging into this enterprise makes any sense.
我不是想彻底阻止你
I'm not trying to definitively stop ya.
只是想放慢你的节奏
Just maybe slow your roll.
也许先让你平静  营造某种安全感的错觉
Maybe go on for some lullin', false sense of security-wise.
-我不会等了  尤金  -那只是在犯傻
- I'm not waiting, Eugene. -That's just being stupid.
蠢货  你根本不知道自己在说什么
Pendejo, you don't know what the hell you're talking about.
我想我知道
I think I do.
我彻底分析了局势
I've analyzed this top to bottom.
不管你是偷袭
It doesn't matter if you're stealthy,
狙击  用枪或者用刀
snipey, gun, or knifey.
亚伯拉罕是对的  他们人多
Abraham was right -- they have the numbers.
他占优势  想要对付他
His ballgame, unless we put together
除非我们集中人力  有人领导
a finishing move for a force of many,
集中力量放大招
along with the man in charge.
一颗子弹解决不了任何问题
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.
最好的情况下  也许你能打死他
Best case, maybe you take him out.
那就给我做一颗子弹
Then make me a bullet.
有人会付出代价的
Somebody has to pay the price.
即便你情愿奉献自己
Even if you're willing...
就我们目前所知  牺牲的也不一定会是你
from all we've seen, it's not a lock you'll be the one.
杀了我们救命恩人的人该不该死
Will the man who killed the man who saved our lives die?
-也许吧  -那就给我做颗子弹
- Maybe. - Then make me a bullet.
你劝服不了我  尤金
You're not talking me out of this, Eugene!
你欠我的  你也欠他的
You owe me, and you owe him.
如果有代价  我来承担
And if there's a price, I'll pay it.
但你不能告诉我不行
But don't you tell me no.
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything.
你什么都不做
You don't do anything.
你是个懦夫
You're a coward.
你是个弱者
And you're weak.
你之所以还活着
The only reason you're alive
是因为你撒谎  大家同情你
is because you lied and because people feel sorry for you.
所以  这一次
So, for once...
做点有用的事
do something useful...
给我做颗子弹
...and make me a bullet.
不要怪自己
Don't beat yourself up.
我为什么要怪自己
Why would I?
他
He --
他问了你马克和安珀的事
He asked you about Mark and Amber,
你出卖了他们  对吧
and you sold 'em out, right?
你不得不这样
You had to.
并不是这样的
That's not what happened.
你晚上能安睡就好
Whatever helps you sleep at night.
你怎么睡得着
How do you sleep at night?
我不睡
I don't.
我看电视直到天明
I watch TV straight to the morning.
当我们跟他定下协议时
When we made that deal with him,
那是我们做出的决定
that was us deciding something.
那本该只影响到我们
This was only supposed to affect us.
不
No.
只要你还站着
If you're still standing,
那就是站在别人背上
then it's always on somebody else's back.
你该走了  会被人看见的
You should go. Someone's going to see us.
我们没做什么
We're not doing anything.
对  我们没做
No. We're not.
我能遮住脸了吗
Can I wrap up my face now?
不  绝对不行
No, you absolutely cannot.
为什么不行
Why the hell not?!
瞧瞧这硬汉
Look at this badass.
不行是因为我还没玩够你
You can't because I'm not done with you.
我喜欢看着你恶心的
And I like looking at your disgusting,
酷酷的  屌屌的眼睛  所以不准遮
rad-ass, badass eye, so it's staying out.
怎么
What?
你有话说吗
You got something to say?
你为什么不杀我
Why haven't you killed me?
或我爸爸  或达里尔
Or my dad or Daryl?
达里尔
Daryl...
会成为我的好战士
is gonna make a good soldier for me.
他以为自己扛得住
You see, he thinks he's holding it together...
但你看见了
but you saw it.
你爸爸
Your dad?
他已经开始给我好东西了
He's already getting me great stuff.
至于你嘛
You, on the other hand...
走着瞧吧
Well, we shall see.
击溃你更有成效
It's more productive to break you.
也更有趣
More fun, too.
你觉得这很蠢吗
You thinking that's stupid?
我觉得我们不同
I'm thinking we're different.
你是个聪明孩子
You're a smart kid.
你认为我该怎么做
What do you think I should do?
你知道我不能放走你
You know I can't let you go.
那么  我该杀了你吗
So, do I kill you?
烫你的脸
Iron your face?
砍掉你的胳膊
Chop off your arm?
告诉我
Tell me.
你看该怎么办
What do you think?
我看你该跳窗
I think you should jump out the window
省下我杀你的麻烦
to save me the trouble of killing you.
这才是那个让我印象深刻的小子
Now, there is the kid that impressed the hell out of me.
我认为你不说你要对我做什么
I think you're not saying what you're gonna do to me
是因为你什么都不会做
because you're not going to do anything.
如果你了解我们  如果你了解那些事
If you knew us, if you knew anything,
你会杀了我们的
you would kill us.
但是你不能
But you can't.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
也许我不能
Maybe I can't.
我们去兜兜风  孩子
Let's go for a ride, kid.
达里尔
Daryl!
你看起来很担心  所以我要带这孩子回家
You seem worried, so I'm taking the kid home.
如果你敢对他做任何事
If you do anything to him --
德怀特
Dwight!
达里尔需要静静
Daryl needs a time-out.
让他进小屋里待待
Put him back in his box for a while.
(趁现在快走)
放下枪
Drop it.
还有你的刀
Your knife, too.
然后呢  你要我的鞋吗
What next? You want my shoes?
带我去找尼根
Take me to Negan.
发动  我们走
Start it up. Let's go.
带我...去找尼根
Take me...to Negan.
-卡尔  在哪...  -伊妮德没事
- Carl, where's -- - Enid's fine.
很好  很好  很好
Great, great, great, great, great, great!
瑞克在哪
Where's Rick?
我
Uh, I --
-我只是...  -不在乎
- I'm just -- - Don't care
瑞克在哪
Where's Rick?
出去给你找补给了
Um, out scavenging for you.
不错
Cool.
我会等
I'll wait.
他去的地方很远
Um...he went out pretty far.
他们今天也许回不来
They might not be back today.
我们一切物资都很缺
We're running really low on everything.
我们差不多要饿死了
We're practically starving here.
饿死
Starving?
就你
You?
"差不多"指的是"还没有"吧
By "Practically," You mean "Not really."
不是吧
Really?
你们这些人真是没幽默感
You people seriously don't have a sense of humor.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你叫什么来着
What's your name again?
奥利维亚
Olivia.
对
Right.
奥利维亚
Olivia.
很抱歉刚才对你无礼
I am sorry for having been so rude to you just now.
看起来我要在这里待一会儿
And it looks like I'm gonna be here for a while,
等待你们无畏的领袖归来
awaiting your fearless leader's return.
如果你愿意
And if you'd like...
我觉得让我干你一炮
I think it would be enjoyable...
一定会很享受
to screw your brains out.
我是说  如果你同意的话
I mean, if, you know, you're agreeable to it.
我对你的喜欢又增加了50%
I am about 50% more into you now.
只是说说
Just sayin'.
好了  我要把脚翘起来
All right, well, I'm just gonna put my feet up
等着我的东西抵达这里了
and wait for my stuff to get here.
奥利维亚
Olivia...
你能做个乖孩子  给我们冲点柠檬水吗
would you be a lamb and make us a little lemonade?
我知道我给你们留了一些粉类的好东西
Now, I know I left you all some of that good powdered stuff.
我应该要去...
Well, I'm supposed to be with --
去冲
Make it.
慢慢来
Take your time.
冲好点
Make it good.
好了  孩子
All right, kid!
带我参观吧
Take me on the grand tour.
这个房间呢
How about this one?
只有一个热水器
Oh, I-it's just a water heater --
你是认真的吗  孩子  拜托
Are you serious, kid? Come on.
天啊
Oh-ho, my.
看看这个小天使
Look at this little angel.
这家伙  他有枪
This guy -- he's armed.
食物  补给  弹药
Has food, supplies, ammo.
"如果你看到这里还没中枪
"The only way that you have possibly read this far
那只可能是我死了"
without being shot is that I am dead."
看起来他保护了自己的补给
Looks like he protected his supplies.
看起来补给依然被保护着
Looks like they're still protected.
只有今天  对吗
Today and only today, right?
对
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
我对我说过的话道歉
I'm sorry for what I said.
我拒绝接受
I reject that.
我真的很抱歉
I am sorry.
不
No.
嘴上道歉  心里没有
Maybe the words, but not the intent.
你语气很真诚  但只是在耍猴
You sound sincere, but it's just a flea circus.
你得到了想要的东西
You got what you wanted.
这不过是你感到内疚
This is just you feeling bad
不代表你说的不是真心话
and not saying that you didn't mean what you said.
你是真心的  你是那样想的
You meant it, you felt it.
这是事实
That's your truth.
尤金
Eugene...
我现在想回到尴尬的沉默中
I'd like to take it back to awkward silence now.
找到想要的东西了吗
Find what you wanted?
算是吧
Did just fine.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
你是从哪里找到的
Where did you acquire all this?
拉丁语
Latin.
那是门痛苦难熬的课
It was a pain-in-the-ass class.
我妈妈说那痛苦总有一天会有回报
My mom said that pain would be useful someday.
这是一个有计划的死人的贮藏清单
It's a list of caches from a dead guy with a plan.
我挖出了医药用品  净水器  照明弹
Dug up medical supplies, water purifiers, flares...
而你会全部都给他们
And you're just gonna give it all to them.
这是瑞克要我们做的  对吧
That's what Rick wants us to do, right?
所以我会这样做
So that's what I'm gonna do.
我还会做更多
I'm gonna do more than that.
他们来了
They're here.
他来了
He's here.
这小姑娘真可爱
Oh, this little girl is precious.
你好  邻居
Hey, neighbor.
晚点过来做客吧
Why don't you come by later?
我们也许会烧烤
We might grill out.
我喜欢这里
Oh, I like it here.
说不定我会住下
I might just have to stay here.
我在想你之前说的话  卡尔
You know, I was thinking about what you said earlier, Carl.
也许让你和你爸爸活着是很蠢
Maybe it is stupid keeping you and your dad alive.
我何必这么努力呢
I mean, why am I trying so hard?
也许我应该把你们俩埋在某个花坛里
Maybe I should just bury you both down in one of those flower beds.
然后自己住在这近郊住宅区里
And then I could just settle into the suburbs.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think about that?